<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gempir</title><link>https://gempir.com/</link><description>Recent content on Gempir</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gempir.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My story of storing chat logs</title><link>https://gempir.com/blog/logs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gempir.com/blog/logs/</guid><description>A few years ago I was feeling creative and thought an IRC chat bot would be a great output for my creativity. IRC itself wasn&amp;rsquo;t really that common anymore, but an up and coming streaming site named twitch.tv was using IRC to run the chat used by thousands of viewers. I started writing on this bot with simple features like the current time or repeating what I would say if I issue the command to do so.</description></item><item><title>Imprint</title><link>https://gempir.com/static/imprint/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 12:28:33 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gempir.com/static/imprint/</guid><description>Owner Daniel Pasch-Sannapiu
gempir.dev@gmail.com
Privacy Policy This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which gempir collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a &amp;ldquo;User&amp;rdquo;) of the gempir.com website (&amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo;). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by gempir.
Personal identification information We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.</description></item><item><title>Why you should think twice about using LastPass</title><link>https://gempir.com/blog/lastpass/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gempir.com/blog/lastpass/</guid><description>As a small disclaimer: I am a PHP developer in my day job and I love PHP. This is in no way a criticism of PHP.
I wanted to start using a password manager, since i’ve heard a lot about them and a lot of good things. The first one coming to my mind was LastPass because I have heard it somewhere on reddit or so before. After creating an account, I wanted to add 2-Factor-Authentication, because losing my LastPass account would equal losing every password of mine.</description></item></channel></rss>